Franz Waxman Papers
Franz Waxman Papers
- Scores by others
  - Scores by others annotated by Franz Waxman
    - Mahler, Gustav. Symphony No. 9 D Minor, London: Boosey & Hawkes Ltd., circa 1941 (Box 22)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Zweite Symphonie C-Moll, Wien- Leipzig: Universal Edition. A.G., circa 1897 (Box 22)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix. Ein Sommernachtstraum, undated (Box 22)
    - Peragallo, Mario. Concerto per Violino e Orchestra, Bryn Mawr, Pennsylvania: Theodore Presser Company, undated (Box 22)
    - Prokofieff, S., Symphony No. 4, New York: Independent Music Publishers, undated (Box 22)
    - Reil, Roger. Piano Concerto #1 in E Minor, undated (Box 22)
    - Robinson, Earl. Abe Lincoln Comes Home, undated (Box 22)
    - Robinson, Earl. The Lonesome Train, New York: Decca Records, Inc., circa 1944 (Box 22)
    - Schreker, Franz. Der Schatzgraber, Wein-Liepzig: Universal-Edition A.G., circa 1944 (Box 22)
    - Schumann, Robert. Concerto, Violoncello and Orchestra, A Minor, Op. 129, New York: Broude Bros., undated (Box 22)
    - Shostakovich, Dimitri. Eighth Symphony, Moscow: State Music Publishers, 1946 (Box 22)
    - Shostakovich, Dimitri. Symphony No. 4, Moscow: Soviet Composer, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Stephan, Rudi. Die Ersten Menschen, Mainz: B. Schott's Sohne, c1915 (Box 23)
    - Tschaikowsky, P. Romeo et Juliette, Paris, etc.: Moscou chez P. Jurgenson, undated (Box 23)
    - Tschaikowsky, P. Funftr Symphonie, Leipzig, etc.: D. Rather, undated (Box 23)
    - Tschaikowsky, Peter Ilyitch. Symphony No. 6 (Pathetique) Op. 74, in B Minor, New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, undated (Box 23)
    - Verdi, Giuseppe. La Traviata, New York: Broude Brothers, undated (Box 23)
    - Vincent, John. Symphonic Poem After Descartes, New York: Mills Music, Inc., c1960 (Box 23)
    - Weber, Carl Maria von. Overture of the Great Heroic-Romantic Opera Euryanthe, London: Ernst Eulenburg, Ltd., undated (Box 23)
    - Weber, Carl Maria von. Euryanthe Ouverture, Leipzig: Breitkopf & Hartel, undated (Box 23)
  - Scores by others, without annotations
    - Antheil, George. Shelley's Fragments, 1950 (Box 23)
    - Brunelli, Louis Jean. Burlesca for Orchestra, undated (Box 23)
    - Jones, John Kester. Spoon River, circa 1961 (Box 23)
    - Korngold, Erich Wolfgang. The Private Lives of Elizabeth and Essex (Warner Bros.), 1939; conductor's score (reproduction) (Box 23)
    - Lackner, Stephan. Nostalgia Tango, circa 1960 (Box 23)
    - Lieberman, Rol., The Song of Life and Death, New York: Associated Music Publishers, Inc., undated (Box 23)
    - Malipiero, G. Francesco. Concerti, Milano: G. Ricordi & Co., circa 1931 (Box 23)
  - Scores by others, arranged by Franz Waxman
    - Dvorak, Anton. Humoresque, Opus 101 No. 7, Westport, Connecticut: Fidelio MusicPublishing Company, undated (Box 24)
    - Enesco, Georges. Romanian Rhapsody No. 1, Westport, Connecticut: Fidelio MusicPublishing Company, undated (Box 24)
    - Rimsky-Korsakoff, Nicolai. The Flight of theBumblebee, undated (Box 24)
- Scores by Waxman
  - Absolute Quiet (Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer), 1936 (Oversize 1)
    Music cue sheet - May 4, 1936
    Selections - reproductions
  - Ach, wie ist das Leben schon! see Fur'n Groschen Liebe/Ach, wie ist das Leben schon! (Oversize 1)
  - Ach, wie oft kommt die Liebe unverhofft!, See Paprika.
  - Adventures of a Young Man, See Ernest Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man (1962: Twentieth Century-Fox).
  - The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn (M-G-M), 1939
    - Overture for piano sextet, computer files; 7 .mus files
      requires Finale music software
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 2)
      Music cue sheet - Feb. 7, 1939
      Selections - reproductions, some with annotations
      Restoration by Christopher Palmer: Full conductor's score - original; Instrumentation list; Orchestral parts - original; Holograph notes on instrumentation (photocopy)
  - The Adventures of Tom Sawyer (Selznick International Pictures), 1937 (Oversize 3)
    "Music notes 10/22/37" - carbon (2 copies)
    Selections - original
  - Air Force (Warner Bros.), 1943 (Oversize 4)
    Music cue sheet - Feb. 17, 1943
    Selections - original sketches
    Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction with annotations)
  - Alias Nick Beal (Paramount Pictures) (other titles: The Contact; Man Dark Circle; Strange Temptation), 1948 (Oversize 5)
    Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction)
  - Allein in einer grossen Stadt... (Oversize 5.5)
    Piano score - reproduction
  - Anne of the Indies (Twentieth Century-Fox), 1951 (Oversize 6)
    Music cue sheet - Nov. 2, 1951
    Orchestral parts (Selections) - reproductions
    Restoration: Full conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions, some with annotations
  - Arrest & Trial (television series), 1963-1964
    - Cue sheets (Box 17)
      Cue sheets for "Flame in the Dark," "Isn't it a lovely view," and "Whose little girl are you?" plus 20 other episodes
    - Scores (Oversize 6.5)
      "Flame in the Dark": Conductor's score (Selections) - reproduction of original sketches
      "Isn't It a Lovely View": Conductor's score (Selections) - reproduction of original sketches
      "Whose Little Girl Are You": Conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions, some with annotations
  - Arsene Lupin Returns (M-G-M), 1938 (Oversize 7)
    Music cue sheet - Feb. 1, 1938
  - At The Circus (M-G-M), 1939 (Oversize 7.5)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 4, 1939
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions
  - Auld Lang Syne Variations (Oversize 8)
    Piano conductor's score - bound reproduction
    Selections - reproductions (in part from Jascha Heifetz Archive at the Library of Congress)
  - Back From Eternity (RKO Radio Pictures), 1956 (Oversize 8.5)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 5, 1956
    Conductor's score (Selections) - original sketches and reproductions
  - The Bad Man (M-G-M), 1941 (Oversize 9)
    Selections - reproductions, one with annotations
    List of compositions recorded for 1930 version
  - The Battle Hymn of the Republic (Oversize 10)
    Full conductor's score (measures 1-40) - original
    Orchestral parts - originals and reproductions, some with annotations
  - La Belle Croisiere (Paris: Editions Coda), c1934 (Oversize 11)
  - Beloved Infidel (Twentieth Century-Fox), 1959 (Oversize 12)
    See also Classic Film Themes Medley [I] and Nostalgic Film Themes.
    Music cue sheet (recording date Oct. 30, 1959)
    Full conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions
    Restoration: Full conductor's score (Selections) - originals and reproductions, some with annotations
  - The Big Bankroll, See King of the Roaring '20's.
  - The Black-Foxe March (New York: Boosey & Hawkes), circa 1959 (Oversize 13)
  - The Blue Danube / Johann Strauss, arranged by by Franz Waxman (Oversize 14)
    Full conductor's score - original and reproduction
  - The Blue Veil (RKO Radio Pictures), 1951 (Oversize 15)
    Music cue sheet - June 13, 1952
  - Boom Town (M-G-M), 1940 (Oversize 16)
    Music cue sheet - July 31, 1940
    Music notes July, 1940
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions, some with annotations
  - The Bride of Frankenstein (Universal Pictures), 1935
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 17A)
      A: Photocopied list of numbers in film. 3 copies.
      B: Autograph (signed) draft of short score (pencil). A few numbers: Conductor's short score (black ink with pencil markings). (1) No. 1. Main title ([4] pp.).; (2) No. 2. Prolog (11 pp.).; (3) No. 3. Monster entrance ([4] pp.).; (4) No. 4. Processional march ([4] pp.).; (5) No. 5. Priest music ([1] p.).; (6) No. 6. Vision music ([2] pp.).; (7) No. 7. Entrance Pretorius ([2] pp.).; (8) No. 8. "You will need a coat" ([3] pp.).; (9) No. 9. Bottle-sequence (4 pp.).; (10) No. 11. Pastorale (7 pp.).; (11) No. 12. Cruixcruf music [sic] ([3] pp.).; (12) No. 13. [Untitled] ([2] pp.) Also: No. 13. Monster breaks out. Conductor's short score (black ink with pencil markings) (4 pp.).; (13) No. 15. arranged by of Schubert: 'Ave Maria' ([1] p.).; (14) No. 16. Violin solo ([1] p.).; (15) No. 17. Fire in the hut (2 pp.).; (16) No. 18. Graveyard ([2] pp.).; (17) No. 19. Dance Macaraw. Conductor's short score (black ink with pencil markings) ([4] pp.).; (18) No. 20. [Untitled] ([1] p.). Also: No. 20. Monster enters #2. Conductor's short score (black ink with pencil markings) ([2] pp.).; (19) No. 21. [Untitled] [(1) p.). Also: No. 21. Miniature shot of tower. ([1] p.).; (20) No. 22A. [Untitled] ([1] p.). Also: No. 22A. [Untitled]. Conductor's short score (black ink with pencil markings) ([1] p.).; (21) No. 22B. Creation I part (7 pp.).; (22) No. 23. Creation sequ. II part ([12] pp.).
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. (Oversize 17B)
      A. No. 2. Full score (pencil) (36 pp.); B. No. 3. Full score (pencil) (9 pp.); C. No. 7. Full score (pencil) (7 pp.); D. No. 8. Full score (pencil) (11 pp.); E. No. 10. Full score (pencil) (7 pp.); F. No. 14. Mysterioso. Full score (pencil) (7 pp.). No. 14A. (17 pp.); G. No. 18. Full score (pencil) (6 pp.); H. No. 19. Autograph (signed) draft of short score (pencil) (3 pp.). and No. 19. Danse macabre. Full score (pencil) (11 pp.); I. [possibly female monster music] Autograph draft of short score (pencil) ([2] pp.). and No. 23. Full score (pencil) (42 pp.).
    - Bride of Frankenstein: Symphonic Suite. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by Clifford Vaughan, arranged by Charles Gerhardt, Newton Wayland and Steven Bernstein. (Oversize 17C)
      A. Front matter of full score (photocopy); B. Part I, re-orchestrated by Steven Bernstein. Conductor's full score (41 pp.) (photocopy); C. 'The Creation of the Monster', re-orchestrated by Newton Wayland. Conductor's full score ([43] pp.) (photocopy)
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17D.1)
      No. 19. Creation sequence. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). With Parts Sheet from Themes and Variations, Westport, Connecticut.
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. "Complete set of parts from Silva Soundtrack Recording." Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17D.2)
      A. No. 17. Danse macabre. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); B. No. 18. Monster enters 2. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); C. No. 20. Finale: The tower explodes. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). With Parts Sheet from Themes and Variations, Westport, Connecticut; D. No. 21. End titles. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). With Parts Sheet from Themes and Variations, Westport, Connecticut.
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17E.1)
      A. No. 1. Titles. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). B. No. 2. Prologue. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). C. No. 3. Monster enters no. 1. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). D. No. 4. Processional march. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy). E. No. 5. A strange apparition. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy).
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17E.2)
      A. No. 6. Pretorius enters. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); B. No. 7. You will need a coat. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); C. No. 8. Bottles. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); D. No. 9. Female monster. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); E. No. 10. Pastorale. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy).
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17F.1)
      A. No. 11. Village / chase. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); B. No. 12. Crucifixion. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); C. No. 13. Monster breaks out. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy).
    - Bride of Frankenstein, film score. Franz Waxman, orchestrated by C. Vaughan. Silva Soundtrack Recordings. (Oversize 17F.2)
      A. No. 14. Ave maria. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); B. No. 15. Fire in the hut. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy); C. No. 16. Graveyard. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple strings) (photocopy).
    - Bride of Frankenstein, Monster Entrance, Prologue, Suite, computer files; 119 .mus files
  - The Bride Wore Red (M-G-M), 1937 (Oversize 17.5)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 2, 1937
  - British Grenadiers, See The Virgin Queen (1955: Twentieth Century-Fox).
  - Cafe Waltzes for Orchestra (Oversize 18)
    Full conductor's score restorations of selections from:
    Hotel Berlin
    In Our Time
    Rector's Restaurant
  - Captains Courageous (M-G-M), 1937; 1977 (Oversize 19)
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) (bound reproduction)
    Restoration, "Bell System Presents" broadcast / Allyn Ferguson, composer: Music cue sheet - Dec. 4, 1977
    Restoration, Suite / arranged by by Christopher Palmer: Full conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions
  - Career (Paramount Pictures), 1959 (Oversize 20)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 23, 1959
  - Carmen Fantasie, See Humoresque (1947: Warner Bros.).
  - The Charm Bracelet, sole agent: Alexander Broude, Inc.
    - The Charm Bracelet (New York: Tetra Music Corp.), 1949 (Oversize 21)
    - The Charm Bracelet (New York: Tetra Music Corp.), 1978 (Oversize 21)
    - The Charm Bracelet: Five Pieces for Violin and Piano (Westport, Connecticut: Fidelio Music Publishing Company), undated (Oversize 21)
  - A Christmas Carol (M-G-M), 1938
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 22)
      Music cue sheet - Dec. 7, 1938
      Piano conductor's score (Selections) (bound reproduction with annotations and with additional copy of music cue sheet mounted on endpaper)
    - Miscellaneous, computer files; 30 .mus files
  - Cimarron (M-G-M), 1960 (Oversize 22.5)
    Music cue sheet - Jan. 23, 1961
  - Classic Film Themes Medley [I] (Oversize 23)
    Restoration of full conductor's score (selections) from Suspicion, My Geisha, Beloved Infidel
  - Classic Film Themes Medley [II] (Oversize 24)
    Restoration of full conductor's score (selections) from The Philadelphia Story, A Place in the Sun, This is My Love, Katsumi from Sayonara
  - Classic Love Themes Medley (Oversize 25)
    Restoration of full conductor's score (selections) from Peyton Place, Rosanna from Ernest Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man, Elephant Walk, The Lost Command
  - Clown on a Tightrope, See Man on a Tightrope (1953: Twentieth Century-Fox).
  - Come Back, Little Sheba (Paramount Pictures), 1953
    - Reminiscences for piano sextet, computer files; 7 .mus files
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 26)
      Music cue sheet - Nov. 14, 1952
      "Music notes... June 10, 1952" - carbon
      Restoration of "Reminiscences": Full conductor's score - original and reproductions with some annotations; Orchestral parts (Selections) - original
  - Confidential Agent (Warner Bros.), 1945 (Oversize 26.5)
    Music cue sheet - Nov. 7, 1945
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) - original sketches and reproductions, some with annotations
  - The Contact Man, See Alias Nick Beal (1948: Paramount Pictures).
  - Count Your Blessings (M-G-M), 1959 (Oversize 27)
    Music cue sheet - May 12, 1959
    Piano conductor's score (Selection) - "Theme From Count Your Blessings" (New York: Robbins Music Corporation, c1959)
  - The Creation of the Monster, See The Bride of Frankenstein (1935: Universal Pictures).
  - Crime in the Streets (Allied Artists), 1956
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28A.1)
      A: Photocopied list of music (listing each scene name, giving the reel & part) used in the production of Crime in the Streets (1955), produced by Vincent M. Fennelly, Lindbrook Productions, Inc. at Goldwyn Studio in Hollywood, November 1955, released by Allied Artists.
      Reel 1 Part 1. Main Title. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28A.2)
      A: (1) Reel 2 Part 1. Glasses. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). (2) Reel 2 Part 2. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). Includes Reel 2 Part 2. Autograph (signed) full score (black ink) (2 p.). (3) Reel 2 Part 3. The billiard ball. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
      B: (1) Reel 3 Part 1. Frankie gets slapped. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). (2) Reel 3 Part 2. Dance sequence. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Includes 'Instrumental Break-down of Musical Numbers', dated Jan. 30th, 1956 (black ink on transparency paper) (1 large folded page).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28A.3)
      A: (1) Reel 4 Part 1. Frankie brooding. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). Includes Reel 4 Part 1. '24 fr. clix'. Handwritten on full-score manuscript paper (black and red ink) (4 leaves.). (2) Reel 4 Part 2. Ben tries again. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
      B: Reel 5 Part 2. The alley. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score, record version. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28B.1)
      A: Section 1. Autograph (?) full score (black, red and blue pencil) ([50] pp.). Includes in Coda: The Alley (R5 P2).
      B: Section 2. Autograph (?) full score (black, red and blue pencil) ([60] pp.). Includes Ben tries again (R4 P2), Frankie brooding (R4 P1), The billiard ball (R2 P3), The plan (R7 P2), McAllister (R10 P2),
    - Crime in the Streets, film score, record version. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28B.2)
      Part 1. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (including black ink additions and corrections with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score, record version. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28B.3)
      Part 2. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28B.4)
      A: (1) Reel 7 Part 1. Santa Lucia. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink). Includes Reel 7 Part 1. Full score (signed Leonard Raab) (pencil) (8 p.). (2) Reel 7 Part 2. The plan. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28B.5)
      A: (1) Reel 9 Part 1, Reel 10 Part 1. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). (2) Reel 10 Part 2. McAllister. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed (with pencil markings). Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink). (3) Reel 10 Part 3. End title. Full set of orchestral parts (multiple copies). Some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings). Some mimeographed. Some hand copied on transparencies (black ink).
    - Crime in the Streets, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 28C)
      A: (1) Reel 1 Part 1. Main title. Autograph short score (black pen) ([12] p.). With script cues ('10-1/2 fr. clix') above staves (black and red ink). (2) Crime in the Streets suite. Draft score for Eng. horn and piano (blue ink) ([1] p.). (3) Reel 2 Part 2. Glasses. Autograph short score (black and red pen with pencil markings) ([1] leaf). (4) Reel 2 Part 3. The billiard ball. Autograph short score (black and red pen with pencil markings) ([1] leaf). (5) Reel 4 Part 1. Frankie brooding. Autograph short score (black, blue and red pen) (2 p.). (6) Reel 4 Part 2. Ben tries again. Autograph short score (black and red pen with pencil markings) (2 p.). (7) Reel 5 Part 2. The alley. Autograph short score (black and red pen with pencil markings) (5 p.). (8) Reel 7 Part 2. The plan. Autograph short score (black pen with pencil markings) ([3] p.). (9) Reel 9 Part 1, Part 10 Part 1. Autograph short score (black pen and pencil) ([11] p.). With script cues ('20 fr. clix') above staves (black and red ink). (10) Reel 10 Part 2. McAllister. Autograph short score (black pen with pencil markings) ([1] leaf). (11) Reel 10 Part 3. End title. Autograph short score (black pen with pencil markings) ([1] leaf). (12) Autograph (?) full score (black, red and blue pencil) ([33] pp.). Includes Glasses (R2 P1), Frankie gets slapped (R3 P1), (R9 P1 & R10 P1), End title (R10 P3).
      B: Autograph (?) full score (black, red and blue pencil) ([47] pp.). Includes Main title (R1 P1).
      C: Autograph (?) full score (black, red and blue pencil) (26 leaves).
    - Miscellaneous, computer files; 54 .mus files
  - La Crise est Finie (Films Paramount), 1934
    - "In a Parisian Cabaret" medley (On Ne Voit Ca Qu’a Paris, Sans Un Mot, and La Crise Est Finie), computer files; 26 .mus files
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 29)
      Selections: La Crise est Finie (Paris: Editions Salabert, c1934)
      On Ne Voit Ca Qu'a Paris (Paris: Editions Salabert, 1934) (issued in two parts)
  - Cry Wolf (Warner Bros.), 1947 (Oversize 29.5)
    Music cue sheets - Sep 1946; Apr. 10, 1947
    Full conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions, some with annotations
  - Dark Circle, See Alias Nick Beal (1948: Paramount Pictures).
  - Dark City (Paramount Pictures), 1950 (Oversize 29.7)
    Music cue sheet - June 12, 1950
    Conductor's score (Selections) - reproductions
    Notes (miscellaneous)
  - Dark Passage (Warner Bros.), 1947 (Oversize 30)
    Music cue sheets - Mar 4, 1947; June 24, 1947
    Piano conductor's score - original sketches
  - A Dark World (a radio play) (Oversize 31)
    Conductor's score - original
    Orchestral parts - original
  - Demetrius and the Gladiators (Twentieth Century-Fox), 1954 (Oversize 32)